ADHURIM CANHASI

Aspiring Computer and Mechanical Engineer

CONTACT

- +383 46-131-115
- ✓ adhurimc@gmail.com
- Martirët e Studimes. Mitrovicë
- - adhurimcanhasi22.github.io
- in/adhurim-canhasi
- adhurimcanhasi22

EDUCATION

2022 - Present **UNIVERSITY OF MITROVICA**

· Bachelor of Computer and Mechanical Engineering

March 2023 - June 2023 UNIVERSITY OF LEOBEN, AUSTRIA

• Bachelor studies with a focus on Machine Learning (Erasmus+ Exchange)

2019 - 2022 FRANG BARDHI HIGH SCHOOL

Mathematics and Natural Science

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C#, Python
- Databases: SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB
- Communication
- Problem-Solving
- Time Management

PROFILE SUMMARY

Final-year student of Computer and Mechanical Engineering at the university of Mitrovica, with past academic exposure to Austria via the Erasmus+ program. Further experience includes software and game development, mechanical design. Solution-oriented, top problemsolving abilities, adaptable. Did extensive soft-skill training that equipped me with excellent communication, teamwork, and leadership skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

K-MOBILE

2020 - PRESENT

Mobile Phone Repair Technician

- Diagnosed and repaired a wide range of mobile hardware and software issues, providing reliable solutions and exceptional customer service.
- Specialized in troubleshooting, screen replacements, battery repairs, and software upgrades for various smartphone models.

AUTOPARTS BESNIKU

JULY 2023 - OCTOBER 2023

Car Diagnostics Specialist

- · Performed diagnostic assessments on a variety of car models at a highly-rated car repair company, identifying and addressing technical and electronic issues.
- · Utilized diagnostic tools and software to accurately pinpoint faults, contributing to timely and cost-effective solutions.

PROJECTS & CODING EXPERIENCE

- GitHub Portfolio: Developed various projects in web development, software engineering, and game development.
- Library Management System: Designed and implemented a database-driven system using C# and MySQL.
- Game Development Project: Created a video game as part of my final university project, showcasing my skills in game mechanics and software design.
- React Native App: Built a task management and leave request system with Firebase integration.

LANGUAGES

- Albanian: Fluent
- English: Fluent
- French: Basics
- German: Basics
- Spanish: Basics

CERTIFICATES

- Digital Perspective Award
- HERAS Plus Soft Skills Training
- English B2/C1
- FRASMIIS+ Traineachin